

920 Windy Hill Street Green Bay.WI 50611 (888) 888-888

Motivated food service professional specializing in resort hospitality. Proven ability to lead, but above bussing tables. Equipped with a certification as a **Certified Restaurant Server with the American Hotel** and Lodging Association, several years of experience, and a natural talent for conflict resolution.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ASSISTANT RESTAURANT MANAGER

Marriott Resort, Green Bay, WI I July 2020 - Present

- Managing and storing vendors' contracts and invoices
- Overseeing restaurant staff performance, ensuring quality dining
- Coordinate communication between front of the house and back of the house staff
- Sets the example for all other staff for service standards, menu knowledge, wine and beverage education, and overall service excellence
- Monitor compliance with safety and hygiene regulations
- Ensure that all guests feel welcome and are given responsive, friendly, and courteous service at all times

SERVER

Green Bay Resort, Green Bay, WI | April 2018 - July 2020

- Stepped up to lead server during holidays with extra staff
- Served as many as 10 tables at one time
- Aided customers with food allergies and dietary restrictions in selecting meals
- Averaged 20% tips per paying customers
- Familiarized guests with menu and daily specials, accurately recording food and drink orders

EDUCATION

FOOD SERVICE MANAGEMENT, **ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE**

HOSPITALITY AND TOURISM MANAGEMENT, CERTIFICATE Madison Community College, Madison, WSeptember 2018 - June 2020

University of Central Florida, OnLineSeptember 2020- November 2020

KEY SKILLS

- **Employee interviewing and scheduling**
- Upselling
- **Supply inventory**
- Mental math
- Deep knowledge of wines and cocktails
- Strong verbal and written communication skills

CERTIFICATIONS

- ♦ Safe Serve Food Safety Manager 2018
- SafeServ Food Handler 2018